Melich, Tanya M.; Papers apap079
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Campaign Files, 1957-2018; Undated; 2; 5.4 cubic ft.
  This series also contains political publications and newsletters such as The National Review and Battle Line. These are filed chronologically within the series. Researchers interested in the campaigns and elections are advised to also look in Series One: Political Files which contains material related to many of the New York and national elections from the late 1950s through the 1970s. Oversized items of interest in this series include a paper shopping bag created for the Nelson A. Rockefeller for Governor campaign, a survey conducted for the Charles Goodell campaign, a map of New York's Congressional Districts, a U.S. Plywood land permit, 1982 New York State convention vote counts, and posters for the Charles Goodell and Jimmy Carter campaigns.
  - Election 1968 NAR Delegate Fight, 1959-1967; Undated (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, N.A Presidential Quest, 1959-1968; Undated (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 2)
  - Lefkowitz for Mayor, 1961—General File (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 3)
  - Lefkowitz for Mayor, 1961—Fact Sheets (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 4-6)
  - Lefkowitz for Mayor, 1961—Position Papers, 1961 June (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 7-10)
  - Lefkowitz for Mayor, 1961—News Clippings (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 11)
  - Casey for Congress 1966—General File (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 12-16)
  - Casey for Congress, 1966—News Clippings (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 17)
  - 1968 Election Analysis—Melich, 1966 (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller for Governor Tote Bag, 1966 (Oversized 1)
  - Nixon and Agnew, 1968—General File (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 19)
  - Nixon and Agnew, 1968—"Winning with Nixon-Agnew in New York State" (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 20-29)
  - Election 1968—NAR Campaign, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 30)
  - Election 1968—Rockefeller Staff, Undated (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 31)
  - Reagan/Rockefeller—General File, 1968; Undated (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 32-34)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—"Trial Heats Nixon, Rockefeller, Humphrey, McCarthy, and Wallace" (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 35)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Position Papers and Reports (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 36)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Finance Committee (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 37)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Republican National and State Committees (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 38-39)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Republican National Convention (Box 1 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 40-42)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Republican National Convention (Delegates) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 1)
  - Campaign Files, Rockefeller for President, 1968—Republican National Convention (Rockefeller Opponent) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller for President 1968—Republican National Convention (Post-Convention Letters) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files, General Delegate Count (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Alabama) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Alaska) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Arizona) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Arkansas) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (California) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 9-15)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Colorado) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Connecticut) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Delaware) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (District of Columbia) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Florida) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 20-24)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Georgia) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 25-27)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Hawaii) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 28)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files(Idaho) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 29-30)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Illinois) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 31)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Indiana) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 32)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Iowa) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 33)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Kansas) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 34)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Kentucky) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 35)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Louisiana) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 36)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Maine) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 37)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Maryland) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 38)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Massachusetts) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 39)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Michigan) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 40)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Minnesota) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 41)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Mississippi) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 42)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Missouri) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 43)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Montana) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 44)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Nebraska) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 45)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Nevada) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 46)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (New Hampshire) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 47)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (New Jersey) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 48)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (New Mexico) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 49)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (New York), 1967-1968 (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 50)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (North Carolina) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 51-52)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (North Dakota) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 53)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Ohio) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 54)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Oklahoma) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 55)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Oregon) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 56-57)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Pennsylvania) (Box 2 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 58-59)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Pennsylvania) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Puerto Rico) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Rhode Island) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (South Carolina) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (South Dakota) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Texas) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 7-8)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Utah) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Washington) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (West Virginia) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—Delegate Files (Wyoming) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Rockefeller for President, 1968—State Committees (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 14)
  - Charles E. Goodell, 1970—New York County Visits (Albany- Dutchess) (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 15-18)
  - Charles E. Goodwell, 1970—New York Tallies by Ethnic or Religious Group (Box 3 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 19)
  - Charles E. Goodell, 1970—Survey (Oversized 2)
  - CREEP—Publications, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 1-2)
  - CREEP—New York State, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 3)
  - CREEP—Telephone Campaign, General File, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 4-5)
  - CREEP—Telephone Campaign Planning Notebook, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 6)
  - CREEP—Telephone Campaign Phone Center Chairman's Notebook, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 7-8)
  - CREEP—Telephone Campaign—Daily Phone Tally, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 9-13)
  - CREEP—Telephone Campaign—Closing the Phone Centers, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 14)
  - CREEP—Telephone Campaign—Report, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 15)
  - Election 1974, Cornelia Netter-66 Assembly District Statistics, Voter Analysis, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 16)
  - Election 1974, Cornelia Netter-66 Assembly District, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 4 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 17)
  - Election 1974 Connie Netter for Assembly—Issues, Undated (Box 5 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 1)
  - Campaign Files, Hugh Carey, 1978—Market Opinion Research (Box 5 (2-Campaign Files), Folder 2)
- ABC Election Research Unit, 1960-1965; Undated; 3; 1.6 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically by events occurring during the 1964 election cycle.
  Tanya Melich was director of the Election Research Unit for ABC News during the 1964 Republican National Convention. As a result, she accumulated numerous papers regarding the presidential primaries in New Hampshire and California, as well as the Republican National Convention and inaugural celebration. The series includes voting reports and analysis, general information on the convention, schedules, biographical information of candidates and platforms, committee meeting notes, and news clippings. The series begins with the New Hampshire primary in March, continues with the California and later primaries, the Republican National Convention in July, and ends with the inauguration of 1965.
  Each primary had a Facts Book created by the news unit. The Facts Book outlines details about the Election Day and gives information about candidates and election issues. The News and Numbers folders include news stories and numbers from the night of the election. General Files may include notes about the news coverage, sample ballots, maps of election districts, and related items. Materials for the California primary also include a few items related to the Democratic Party and a 37 page document titled the "Christian, Anti-Communist Crusade" which was written by the Christian, Anti-Communist Crusade in 1963 for delivery at the Annual Meeting of the American Political Science Association. The group was concerned with the growth and purpose of extreme right wing political organizations.
  The Republican National Convention of 1964 was held at the Cow Palace in San Francisco. Similar to the primaries, a "Facts Book" was created with information about the candidates, the convention arrangements, voting, and related information. The folder Convention Planning and Arrangements, includes theme plans, hotel arrangements, news clippings and press releases. There are also nomination speeches for Nelson A. Rockefeller, George Romney, William E. Miller and Barry Goldwater to be the presidential candidate. The series also includes remarks and presentations made throughout the convention from a variety of speakers. While Melich had documents concerning several candidates at the convention, she collected an extensive amount of information relating to Goldwater, such as his platform, the growth of the Goldwater movement, and the arguments of his proponents. The State Files include brief notes regarding Republican representation and delegates at the Convention. They are alphabetical by state with United States districts and territories at the end.
  The ABC News Facts Book, Inauguration 1965 gives information about the location and history of the event, biographies of members of Congress, and all the details regarding the inauguration ceremony and ball.
  - Research Unit New Hampshire Primary 1964—Candidates Info (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 1)
  - New Hampshire Primary 1964—Facts Book (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 2)
  - New Hampshire Primary 1964—Miscellaneous Items (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 3)
  - New Hampshire Primary 1964—News Clippings (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 4)
  - New Hampshire Primary 1964—News Clippings, 1964 March 12 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 5)
  - New Hampshire Primary 1964—News + Numbers (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 6)
  - New Hampshire Primary 1964—Past Primaries in N.H. (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 7)
  - New Hampshire Primary 1964—Pre-Primary Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 8)
  - New Hampshire Primary—Primary Report, 1964 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 9)
  - Oregon Primary—Election '64, 1964 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 10)
  - ABC Election Research Unit California Primary 1964—Candidate Info (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 11)
  - California Primary 1964—Christian Anti-Communist Crusade, 1963 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 12)
  - California Primary 1964—Democratic Party Ballots, News Clippings (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 13)
  - California Primary 1964—Facts Book (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 14)
  - California Primary 1964—Miscellaneous Items (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 15)
  - California Primary 1964—News and Numbers (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 16)
  - California Primary 1964—News Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 17)
  - California Primary 1964—Pre-Primary Reports and Items (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 18)
  - California Primary 1964—Primary Election Results, March-May (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 19)
  - California Primary 1964—Statement of Vote (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 20)
  - Election 1964 Primaries, Undated (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 21)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Barry Goldwater (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 22)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Barry Goldwater, Growth of Movement, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 23)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Barry Goldwater Information Kit (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 24)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Goldwater Platform, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 25)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Goldwater, "Stop Goldwater", 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 26)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Committees (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 27)
  - Republican National Convention, 1964—Convention Planning and Arrangements (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 28)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Delegates and Delegations (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 29)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Delegate General Information (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 30)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Delegate Selection, Undated (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 31)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Facts Book (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 32)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Facts Book (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 33)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Floor Strategy, Undated (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 34)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—General Dwight D. Eisenhower, Undated (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 35)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—General News, Undated (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 36)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Henry Cabot Lodge (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 37)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Information about George Romney, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 38)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 39)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—"Official Proceedings of the 20th Republican National Convention" (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 40)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Platform Amendment, Proposals (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 41)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Platform, Anti-Goldwater (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 42)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Platform Committee Members (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 43)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Platform, General (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 44)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Platform States Proposals (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 45)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Platform Text (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 46)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Polls (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 47)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Program and Agenda (Box 1 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 48)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Republican Nominees, 1962-1964; Undated (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 1)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Right-Wing, Undated (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 2)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Rules, 1960; Undated (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 3)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Speeches (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 4)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Staff and Supporters for N. Rockefeller (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 5)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (Alabama-Connecticut) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 6)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (Delaware-Indiana) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 7)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (Iowa-Maryland) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 8)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Sate Files (Massachusetts-Mississippi) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 9)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (Missouri-New Hampshire) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 10)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (New Jersey-North Carolina) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 11)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (North Dakota-Rhode Island) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 12)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (South Carolina-Utah) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 13)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files, Texas Information and News Clippings (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 14)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (Vermont-Wisconsin) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 15)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—State Files (Wyoming, D.C., Puerto Rico, Virgin Islands) (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 16)
  - Republican National Conventions 1964—Tallies, Delegate Votes for Candidates, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 17)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—T. Melich Copy (Box 3 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 1)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—William W. Scantron (Box 3 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 2)
  - Republican National Convention 1964—Young Republicans (Box 3 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 3)
  - Post-Republican National Convention 1964—After Goldwater, 1964-1967; Undated (Box 3 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 4)
  - ABC News Facts Book Inauguration (1-2 of 5), 1965 (Box 3 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 5-6)
  - ABC News Facts Book Inauguration (3-5 of 5), 1965 (Box 4 (3-ABC Election Research Unit), Folder 1-3)
- CBS, Inc., 1961-2009; Undated; 4; 3.4 Cubic Feet
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains materials relating to Tanya Melich's time as an employee of CBS, Inc, as well as materials from the time after her employment. Melich worked at CBS, Inc, in a variety of roles from 1975 until 1981, as the Editor of Corporate Information, the Associate Director of the Public Policy Unit, and as the Director of Civic Affairs within the Corporate Affairs Department. A significant portion of the collection focuses on CBS Polls, and how CBS covered elections, political conventions, etc. There is general information on the company, as well as the Public Policy Study Unit, a group studying the impact of new technology on broadcasting. Documents from a "Management Seminar," including notes, assignments and exercises are also included. Records from the Women's Advisory Committee, which was designed to help women develop their careers at CBS, are of note as well. Related documents to working women include files that pertain to a 1977 suit filed by Melinda Cotton against CBS regarding women's employment and possible discrimination. The folders related to this topic include legal documents, correspondence and articles by Sandra Purnell and Gloria Steinem. Other material in this series comes from the Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies which sponsored a program on communication Melich participated in. Information on communication technology in a more general sense can also be found in this series.
  - CBS'76 + '77, 1969; 1976-1977 (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 1)
  - CBS Public Policy Study Unit, 1971; 1975-1976; Undated (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 2)
  - Women's Advisory Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 3)
  - CBS Misc. Job Information, 1974-1978; Undated (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 4)
  - Public Policy Study Unit—Future of Media, 1976 (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 5)
  - Views towards 1976 Platform Committee—Statement by Arthur Taylor (President, CBS Inc.) (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 6)
  - Public Policy Study Unit Questions, 1976-1978 (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 7)
  - Corporate Affairs Strategic Plan, 1976-1980 (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 8)
  - Advanced Management Seminar 1977—Session Notes, Assignments, etc. (Box 1 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 9-10)
  - Advanced Management Seminar General Information, 1977 (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 1)
  - John D. Backe Notes & Correspondence, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 2)
  - CBS Management School April 16-22, 1978, 1977-1978; Undated (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 3)
  - Women's Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 4)
  - Women's Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 5)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1979 (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 6)
  - CBS—Notes and Agendas, 1979-1981; Undated (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 7)
  - Commission Decisions CBS Network Carter-Mondale Presidential Committee V. ABC, CBS, NBC, 1979 (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 8)
  - United States Court of Appeals CBS, Inc. V. Federal Communications Commission and United States of America Petitions & Briefs, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 9)
  - CBS. Inc Aspen Institute of Humanistic Studies, 1980-1993 (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 10)